{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077385355","data":{"timestamp":" 947077385355"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_456_456-209-476"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 456"," userResponse":" 476"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077394704","data":{"timestamp":" 947077394704"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_456_456-209-476"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 456"," userResponse":" 456"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077416663","data":{"timestamp":" 947077416663"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_802_802-859-628"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 802"," userResponse":" 859"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077427724","data":{"timestamp":" 947077427724"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_802_802-859-628"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 802"," userResponse":" 802"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077457453","data":{"timestamp":" 947077457452"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_608_608-268-703"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 608"," userResponse":" 608"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077497607","data":{"timestamp":" 947077497606"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_619_619-180-743"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 619"," userResponse":" 619"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077525004","data":{"timestamp":" 947077525004"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_859_840-762-859"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 859"," userResponse":" 840"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077535056","data":{"timestamp":" 947077535056"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_859_840-762-859"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 859"," userResponse":" 859"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077596186","data":{"timestamp":" 947077596186"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_393_393-827-713"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 393"," userResponse":" 393"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077637481","data":{"timestamp":" 947077637481"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_776_776-809-606"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 776"," userResponse":" 776"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077734851","data":{"timestamp":" 947077734851"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_662_794-500-662"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 662"," userResponse":" 662"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077790282","data":{"timestamp":" 947077790282"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_166_636-214-166"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 166"," userResponse":" 166"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077819229","data":{"timestamp":" 947077819229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_507_538-770-507"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 507"," userResponse":" 538"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077830543","data":{"timestamp":" 947077830543"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_507_538-770-507"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 507"," userResponse":" 507"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077839120","data":{"timestamp":" 947077839120"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_507_538-770-507"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077844983","data":{"timestamp":" 947077844983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_507_538-770-507"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077851758","data":{"timestamp":" 947077851758"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" 0dfc8afc-4287-4957-9229-c1f849949e64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.79"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_507_538-770-507"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077860672","data":{"timestamp":" 947077860672"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" c5753813-ef92-41fc-9ce6-5b5b68caff6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077863261","data":{"timestamp":" 947077863261"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" c5753813-ef92-41fc-9ce6-5b5b68caff6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077863406","data":{"timestamp":" 947077863406"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000105_160242"," gameId":" c5753813-ef92-41fc-9ce6-5b5b68caff6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}